Web Developer

## **OBJECTIVE**

I aim to become a Web Developer with a reputable company that encourages teamwork, creativity, and continued learning where I have variety in my day. I have spent the last six years working in a tech store and look to convert my troubleshooting experience into skills beneficial in the development industry. I am seeking employment, where I am currently located, in Evansville, IN or would enjoy working remotely as well.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Solutions Specialist, Verizon Wireless**

2016 - 2022

- Successfully implemented solutions for a wide array of cellular customers, creating personal connections to make tech look simple.
- Performed troubleshooting on iOS, android, Bluetooth and Wi-Fi electronics, as well as Verizon software and POS submitting service tickets as required.
- Provided training for new employees through hands-on experience and promoting a culture of continuous improvement.

# Manager, Mark's Mattress Outlet and Fireworks.

2015 - 2016

- Obtained new sales tactics and processes in or to generate maximum amount of sales to potential buyers.
- Worked with Point of Sales, QuickBooks, and Microsoft Office applications.
- Worked independently on most occasions while selling, pricing, ordering new inventory, and working with other managers to coordinate sales and product transfers across other Mark's locations.

# **Inventory Specialist, Walmart Super-center**

2014 - 2015

- Documented inventory using electronic database. Aided management with product display.
- Maximized customer service while managing time wisely to meet merchandise stocking deadlines.

Campus Recreation Assistant, USI Security Personnel, Oakland City University 2012 - 2014

2010 - 2012

### **EDUCATION**

# **CareerFoundry — Full-Stack Web Development Program**

Immersive training program with emphasis on Full-Stack Web Development

University of Southern Indiana — Bachelor's of Science Individual Studies
Oakland City University — Criminal Justice

**Shoals High School — Diploma** 

## **PROJECTS**

## **Portfolio Website**

 A website designed to show potential employers the following projects. Written using HTML and CSS.

## **Pokédex**

 A small web application with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript that loads data from an external API and enables the viewing of data points in detail.

### **NixFlix-Server**

Server side code is A RESTful API coded from scratch using Node.js.

### **NixFlix-Client**

• A client-side frontend for your RESTful API, built with React.

# **Meet-up App**

• A server-less, progressive web app that fetches data from the Google Calendar API.

# **Chat App**

• A JavaScript chat app built with React Native, featuring advanced functionality such as offline storage or geolocation.

# **Quiz App**

• A JavaScript quiz app built with Angular.

### **SKILLS**

•	Η	ΤI	М	ı

CSS

SCSS

Bootstrap

GitHub

Git

Javascript

Express.JS

Node.JS

React

AJAX

jQuery

APIs

SQL

Heroku

Redux

Angular

MongoDB